Hi everyone and welcome to another jumpsuit up video here on my channel and I have a very special
jumpsuit and harness combination for you today. I know that you like see-through jumpsuits so
that's what you're going to see and a matching harness both from Anoises and the clue is that
the jumpsuit is also made to measure. I'll get dressed right away so you don't have to wait any longer.
Thank you.
That was actually really fast because it's super easy to dress. It's stretchy
and really comfortable. I don't know, I really like it. It's also so beautiful. I
think it makes a great figure with the lines here and also with the integrated
fingers the gloves and socks you have really like a whole body suit except for the head now
but there's a mask i'm going to show later there is not only the catsuit i'm showing today but
also a harness matching to the cat suit both from an oasis and i'll try to figure out how to put the
the harness on. No, I already tried once and I'll do it now.
Okay, see you in a bit. This is going to be too confusing to do it on camera.
I managed in the end and this is the combination with the harness. Also, there are the wristlets
here I can attach them oh of course the fabric is a bit slippery if I want to do this by myself
so I can attach them I think it's such an elegant look with the gold and the black leather
and also the whole catsuit is so great. I'm going to take them off completely.
Without the chains it almost looks like normal fashion but of course it's not
just that you can use it at home to play a bit with your partner. But you could
also wear the catsuit to go out to party. I don't know, I think this would be like a red carpet
outfit by Exelon. So if I would be really famous and could wear anything I want to without someone
saying, oh that looks gross or that is too sexy or whatever, I would wear something like this.
and one thing I want to mention is that the mesh fabric here is not a tight fabric
so the same as nylons because I was a bit afraid that I'm going to ruin it instantly with all the
buckles and the leather and that I'm going to rip holes in the delicate fabric here but it works so
and I think it's also because the fabric is a bit more durable than nylons and to
be honest I destroy every tights I own after a while I like to destroy all
tights back to this outfit I just love it I think it looks so great and also
let me turn around
also from the backside
Okay, I promised you a mask and here it is. It's super futuristic and I think it works perfectly with the whole outfit. I'm going to take some really cool pictures with this one.
So to kink this whole outfit completely up, yeah, attach everything and wear the mask.
And I'm trying to put them on without ruining my makeup completely so you have an impression
of how it's going to look.
All right, with the lashes on, I can't really open my eyes.
Without lashes, I tried it, it's fine.
You can see something even if you wear it.
And I think it looks really cool.
So futuristic.
And it takes a bit of time to adjust it so it fits properly.
But yeah, it's not restrictive or anything, it's just for the looks.
What do you think?
With or without mask?
With or without harness?
What do you think of the jumpsuit itself?
You like it?
Leave a comment and I think that was already everything for today, for this jumpsuit up
video.
I hope you enjoyed it and see you in the next video.
Bye!
P.S.
Thanks to Anoasis for sending me this outfit.
It's really cool.